Guide to the Liederkranz Collection ca. 1847-1987 MSS.130
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Printed Sheet Music Collection
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.193., undated (Box 40, Folder 483)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Uniform Title: Meeresstille und gluckliche Fahrt. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: C. 25938, undated (Box 40, Folder 486)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Musikantenprugelei Uniform Title: Musikantenprugelei (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 14951 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 166, Folder 2819)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: O Sons of Art Uniform Title: An die Kunstler, undated (Box 140, Folder 1958)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: On Wings of Song Uniform Title: On Wings of Song; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Ricordi & Co., Inc. Plate Number: N. Y. 698, undated (Box 168, Folder 2923)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ouverture zu den Hebriden (Fingals Hohle) Uniform Title: Hebriden. Ouverture Plate Number: 7848, undated (Box 39, Folder 471)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ouverture zu den Hebriden (Fingals-Hohle) Uniform Title: Hebriden. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.192., undated (Box 39, Folder 472)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ouverture. Die Fingals-Hohle Uniform Title: Hebriden. Ouverture Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: C. 25225., undated (Box 39, Folder 474)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Rondo Capriccioso Uniform Title: Rondo capriccioso Publisher information: Boston: B. F. Wood Music Company Plate Number: B.F.W. 5290-10, undated (Box 145, Folder 2008)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1838., undated (Box 41, Folder 494)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5150-53, undated (Box 41, Folder 495)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture; arr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 14174, undated (Box 41, Folder 493)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Publisher information: Braunschweig (Germany): Henry Litolff's Verlag Plate Number: 10774, undated (Box 41, Folder 491)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Uniform Title: Ruy Blas. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.198., undated (Box 41, Folder 492)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sinfonie fur das grosse Orchester Uniform Title: Symphony no. 1 in c minor, op. 11; arr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1432, undated (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 7852, undated (Box 41, Folder 487)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: M.B.117.*, undated (Box 41, Folder 490)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: M.B.7., undated (Box 41, Folder 489)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Uniform Title: Sommernachtstraum. Scherzo Publisher information: New York: Associated Music Publisher's Inc. (Breitkopf & Härtel [printer]) Plate Number: Orch.B.281., undated (Box 41, Folder 488)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Spinning Song Uniform Title: Songs Without Words. Spinning Song Publisher information: New York: Century Music Publishing Co. Plate Number: 433, undated (Box 159, Folder 2570)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Spring Song Uniform Title: Gesange, op. 19, no. 1. Frühlingslied Publisher information: New York: Richard A. Saalfield, undated (Box 99, Folder 1262)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Spring Song Uniform Title: Songs Without Words. Spring Song Publisher information: New York: Conservatory Publication Society, undated (Box 103, Folder 1379)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphonie No. 1, C minor Uniform Title: Symphony no. 1, op. 11, C minor; arr. Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1379 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphonie No. 5, Op. 107 (Reformation Uniform Title: Symphony no. 5 in D Major, op. 107 (Reformation) Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.81/82, undated (Box 43, Folder 507)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphony no. 1, op. 11 Uniform Title: Erste Symphonie, op. 11 Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: M.B.1./M.B.1*, undated (Box 43, Folder 505)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Symphony no. 2, op. 52 Uniform Title: Lobgesang. Sinfonia Plate Number: 6533, undated (Box 43, Folder 504)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Thanks Be to God Uniform Title: Thanks Be to God Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 10188, undated (Box 173, Folder 3152)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Vierte Symphonie Uniform Title: Symphony no. 4, op. 90, A Major (Italian symphony) Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: M.B.4/M.B.4.*, undated (Box 44, Folder 512)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Volkslied (Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat) Uniform Title: Volkslied, op. 47, no. 4: Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 8003-3, undated (Box 161, Folder 2636)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Volkslied (Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat) Uniform Title: Volkslied, op. 47, no. 4: Es ist bestimmt in Gottes Rat Publisher information: Vienna (Austria): Theodor Rattig (Jos. Eberle & Co., Vienna [printer]) Plate Number: T.R.197., undated (Box 161, Folder 2637)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: War March of the Priests from Athalia Uniform Title: Athalia. War March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1865-25, undated (Box 39, Folder 467)
  - Composer: Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: War march of the Priests from Athalia Uniform Title: Athalia. War March; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1865-30, undated (Box 39, Folder 468)
  - Composer: Mendolssohn-Bartholdy, Felix Title: Die Erste Walpurgisnacht Uniform Title: Erste Walpurgisnacht Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner Plate Number: 1402, undated (Box 42, Folder 500)
  - Composer: Menzel, J. Title: General Stotzer March Uniform Title: General Stotzer; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 9922-17 1/2, undated (Box 123, Folder 1763)
  - Composer: Menzel, J. Title: Kleine susse Maus Uniform Title: Kleine susse Maus, undated (Box 163, Folder 2738)
  - Composer: Merkler, Andor Title: Gipsy Dance (La Tzigane dansante) Uniform Title: Gipsy Dance; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 10603-37, undated (Box 43, Folder 508)
  - Composer: Mertke, Eduard Title: Um Mitternacht Uniform Title: Um Mitternacht Publisher information: Cologne (Germany): P. J. Tonger's Musikverlag (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: P. J. T. 1379 Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated (Box 173, Folder 3154)
  - Composer: Methfessel, A. Title: Der deutsche Sangerbund Uniform Title: Deutsche Sangerbund (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 153, undated (Box 153, Folder 2311)
  - Composer: Metra, Olivier Title: La Serenade. Valse Espagnole Uniform Title: La Serenade. Valse Espagnole; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 3826-14 1/2, undated (Box 43, Folder 509)
  - Composer: Metz, Aug. C. Title: Sweetheart Serenade Uniform Title: Sweetheart Publisher information: Brooklyn: Aug. C. Metz, undated (Box 104, Folder 1417)
  - Composer: Meyer, Herwegh C. Title: Husarenlied Uniform Title: Husarenlied, undated (Box 156, Folder 2450)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Ballet Music. Divertissement Uniform Title: Ballet Music. Divertissement; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 5915-51, undated (Box 45, Folder 523)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Coronation March from The Prophet Uniform Title: Prophete. Marche du sacre; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 15990-42, undated (Box 45, Folder 525)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Der 91ste Psalm Uniform Title: 91. Psalm Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote & G. Bock Plate Number: B.& B. 2426., undated (Box 135, Folder 1901)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Der 91ste Psalm Uniform Title: 91. Psalm Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote & G. Bock Plate Number: B.& B. 2427., undated (Box 135, Folder 1900)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Die Hugenotten. Ouverture Uniform Title: Huguenots. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Orch.B.200., undated (Box 45, Folder 528)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Die Hugenotten. Ouverture Uniform Title: Huguenots. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: Part.B.856., undated (Box 45, Folder 527)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote & G. Bock Plate Number: 6319 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 45, Folder 530)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote & G. Bock Plate Number: 6320 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 45, Folder 531)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: Braunschweig (Germany): C. Weinholtz Plate Number: 1099, undated (Box 45, Folder 532)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz Uniform Title: Fackeltanz no. 1 Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 2082-47, undated (Box 45, Folder 533)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Fackeltanz Uniform Title: Fackeltanz Publisher information: Braunschweig (Germany): Julius Bauer (Engelmann & Muhlberg [printer]) Plate Number: 840 Engraver: Engelmann & Muhlberg, undated (Box 104, Folder 1426)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Kronungsmarsch aus der Oper Der Prophet Uniform Title: Prophete. Marche du sacre Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 8269, undated (Box 45, Folder 524)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Ouverture et Orgie de l'Opera Les Huguenots Uniform Title: Huguenots. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Breitkopf & Härtel Plate Number: 5811, undated (Box 45, Folder 529)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Quartetto Le Prophete Uniform Title: Prophete. Selection, undated (Box 116, Folder 1653)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Sommermorgen aus den Hugenotten von Maierbeer Uniform Title: Huguenots. Selection; arr., undated (Box 170, Folder 3001)
  - Composer: Meyerbeer, Giacomo Title: Star of the North. Selection Uniform Title: Etoile du nord. Selection; arr. Publisher information: Boston: Jean White Plate Number: 1430-47-5, undated (Box 45, Folder 526)
  - Composer: Meyer-Helmund, E. Title: Serenade Roccoco Uniform Title: Serenade Roccoco Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Bosworth & Co. Plate Number: B. & Co. 273, undated (Box 96, Folder 1193)
  - Composer: Meyer-Helmund, Erik Title: Dann ist's die rechte Zeit Uniform Title: Dann ist's die rechte Zeit Plate Number: 7102, undated (Box 153, Folder 2318)
  - Composer: Meyer-Helmund, Erik Title: Venetianisches Gondellied Uniform Title: Venetianisches Gondellied Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Friedrich Kistner (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 6406 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 152, Folder 2282)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Clare Dettin. Vorspiel zum dritten Aufzuge Uniform Title: Clare Dettin. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel Plate Number: 11548 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 48, Folder 584)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Clare Dettin. Vorspiel zum dritten Aufzuge Uniform Title: Clare Dettin. Ouverture Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel Plate Number: 11682, undated (Box 48, Folder 585)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Das Fest Uniform Title: Fest Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 12952 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 101, Folder 1324)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Der Blumen Rache Uniform Title: Blumen Rache Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 12217 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 130, Folder 1872)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Der Blumen Rache Uniform Title: Blumen Rache Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 12219 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 130, Folder 1873)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Die Mondfee Uniform Title: Mondfee Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 17618, undated (Box 174, Folder 3204)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Gebt mir vom Becher nur den Schaum Uniform Title: Op. 100, no. 2. Gebt mir vom Becher nur den Schaum Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22928, undated (Box 162, Folder 2676)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Gothen-Treue Uniform Title: Gothen-Treue Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug & Co. Plate Number: G. H. 1787, undated (Box 157, Folder 2505)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Konigin Waldlieb Uniform Title: Konigin Waldlieb Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9307 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 88, Folder 1106)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Konigin Waldlieb Uniform Title: Konigin Waldlieb Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): C. F. W. Siegel's Musikalienhandlung (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 9308 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 163, Folder 2748)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Tanzreigen Uniform Title: Tanzreigen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug & Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G. H. 2351 Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated (Box 88, Folder 1107)
  - Composer: Meyer-Olbersleben, Max Title: Tanzreigen Uniform Title: Tanzreigen Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Gebruder Hug & Co. (F. M. Geidel, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: G.H.2353. Engraver: F. M. Geidel, Leipzig, undated (Box 101, Folder 1319)
  - Composer: Mezzacapo, E. Title: Sympathie. Valse Uniform Title: Sympathie Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Hawkes & Son Plate Number: H & S. 3591, undated (Box 122, Folder 1757)
  - Composer: Michaelis, Theodor Title: Die Schmiede im Walde Uniform Title: Schmiede im Walde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ruhle & Wendling Plate Number: 218, undated (Box 44, Folder 514)
  - Composer: Michaelis, Theodor Title: Die Schmiede im Walde Uniform Title: Schmiede im Walde Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Ruhle & Wendling Plate Number: R. & W. 217, undated (Box 44, Folder 515)
  - Composer: Minnigerode, Meade, George S. Pomeroy, and Tod B. Galloway Title: The Whiffenpoof Song Uniform Title: Whiffenpoof Song; arr. Publisher information: New York: Miller Music Corporation Plate Number: 579-6, undated (Box 154, Folder 2356)
  - Composer: Miro, Enrique Title: Mercedes. Valse Espagnole Uniform Title: Mercedes. Valse Espagnole; arr. Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer Plate Number: 22532, undated (Box 44, Folder 516)
  - Composer: Moellendorff, Willy von Title: Regenhusch im Fruhjahr Uniform Title: Regenhusch im Fruhjahr Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): D. Rahter Plate Number: 3289, undated (Box 170, Folder 2997)
  - Composer: Mohr, Andreas Title: Festmarsch Uniform Title: Festmarsch, undated (Box 128, Folder 1867)
  - Composer: Mohr, Herman Title: Columbus Uniform Title: Colon Publisher information: Philadelphia: Herman Mohr, undated (Box 151, Folder 2213)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter, undated (Box 120, Folder 1716)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 201 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 155, Folder 2429)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 202 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 155, Folder 2430)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Das Gewitter Uniform Title: Gewitter Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Friedrich Luckhardt (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: F. L. 226 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 155, Folder 2431)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Hoffnung Uniform Title: Hoffnung Publisher information: Schleusingen (Germany): Conrad Glaser (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated (Box 162, Folder 2663)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Hymnus Uniform Title: Jauchzend erhebt sich die Schopfung. Hymnus (Marsh & Co., Philadelphia [printer]), undated (Box 100, Folder 1299)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: Jauchzend erhebt sich die Schopfung. Hymnus Uniform Title: Jauchzend erhebt sich die Schopfung. Hymnus Publisher information: Schleusingen (Germany): Conrad Glaser (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 150 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 100, Folder 1298)
  - Composer: Mohr, Hermann Title: O lieb' so lang du lieben kannst Uniform Title: O lieb' so lang du lieben kannst Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): M. Bahn Verlag (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: M. 3697 B. Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 168, Folder 2905)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Auf Offner See Uniform Title: Auf offner See, undated (Box 96, Folder 1202)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Das Dichtergrab am Rhein Uniform Title: Dichtergrab am Rhein Publisher information: Schleusingen (Germany): Conrad Glaser (F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig [printer]) Engraver: F. W. Garbrecht, Leipzig, undated (Box 155, Folder 2395)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Der Rheingauer Wein Uniform Title: Rheingauer Wein Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 22369.1, undated (Box 169, Folder 2977)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Die Gestirne Uniform Title: Gestirne Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 23081., undated (Box 174, Folder 3202)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Hymne an die Nacht Uniform Title: Hymne an die Nacht Publisher information: Offenbach a/M (Germany): Johann Andre (Kohler & Teller, Offenbach a/M [printer]) Plate Number: 10279, undated (Box 138, Folder 1928)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Im grunen Kranz Uniform Title: Im grunen Kranz Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 3133 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 155, Folder 2398)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: O Fruhlingszeit! Uniform Title: O Furhlingszeit! Publisher information: Leipzig (Germany): Robert Forberg (C. G. Röder, Leipzig [printer]) Plate Number: 3135 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 168, Folder 2928)
  - Composer: Mohring, Ferdinand Title: Vorbei! Uniform Title: Vorbei! Publisher information: Mainz (Germany): B. Schott's Söhne Plate Number: 20077, undated (Box 152, Folder 2289)
  - Composer: Molloy, James L. Title: The Kerry Dance Uniform Title: Kerry Dance Publisher information: New York: G. Schirmer, Inc. Plate Number: 2318, undated (Box 159, Folder 2561)
  - Composer: Monckton, Lionel Title: The Quaker Girl. Selection Uniform Title: Quaker Girl. Selection; arr. Publisher information: London (Great Britain): Chappell & Co. Ltd. Plate Number: 24635, undated (Box 44, Folder 517)
  - Composer: Moniuszko, Stanislaw Title: Mazur z opery Straszny Dwor Uniform Title: Straszny Dwor. Mazur Publisher information: Warsaw (Poland): Warszawskie Towarzystwo Muzyczne Plate Number: W. T. M. 51, undated (Box 111, Folder 1588)
  - Composer: Moniuszko, Stanislaw Title: Soldier's Song Uniform Title: Soldier's Song; arr. Publisher information: New York: Carl Fischer Plate Number: 1337-25, undated (Box 46, Folder 545)
  - Composer: Moniuszko, Stanislaw Title: Tance Goralskie z opery Halka Uniform Title: Halka. Tance Goralskie Publisher information: Warsaw (Poland): Warszawskie Towarzystwo Muzyczne Plate Number: W. T. M. 107, undated (Box 111, Folder 1589)
  - Composer: Morena, Camillo Title: Kinkerlitzchen. Potpourri Uniform Title: Kinkerlitzchen. Potpourri Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote & G. Bock Plate Number: 15908 Engraver: C. G. Röder, Leipzig, undated (Box 44, Folder 518)
  - Composer: Morena, Camillo Title: Kinkerlitzchen. Potpourri Uniform Title: Kinkerlitzchen. Potpourri Publisher information: Berlin (Germany): Ed. Bote & G. Bock Plate Number: 15910, undated (Box 44, Folder 519)
  - Composer: Moret, Neil Title: Hiawatha. A Summer Idyl Uniform Title: Hiawatha Publisher information: Detroit: Whitney-Warner Pub. Co., undated (Box 102, Folder 1345)
  - Composer: Moret, Neil Title: Silver Heels Uniform Title: Silver Heels Publisher information: New York: Jerome H. Remick & Co., undated (Box 102, Folder 1347)
  - Composer: Morley, Thomas Title: Mein schones Lieb Uniform Title: Mein schones Lieb Publisher information: New York Engraver: Otto Lobner, undated (Box 166, Folder 2839)
  - Composer: Morley, Thomas Title: Now is the month of Maying Uniform Title: Now is the month of Maying; arr. Publisher information: Boston: E. C. Schirmer Music Co. Plate Number: E. C. S. 19, undated (Box 168, Folder 2911)
  - Composer: Morley, Thomas Title: Tanzlied Uniform Title: Tanzlied, undated (Box 173, Folder 3148)
  - Composer: Moss, Earle M., arr. Title: Deutsche Volkslieder Uniform Title: Deutsche Volkslieder Publisher information: New York, undated (Box 103, Folder 1382)